We've created a new feature in uh
Business Central which allows the users
to upload an email into the system and
then copilot will look through this
email and find keywords that it can then
use to create a complaint in the system.
Here I have a mail from a customer who
was dissatisfied with some of the
products that they received on a order.
So when I click on this, this uploads
the entire text from the mail into the
prompt for the co-pilot. We can see here
that the customer got the order from an
order number and unfortunately some of
the items have issues. Two of these
items were ordered and there was some
paint peeling off and another one got
damaged during shipment. When I press
generate, Copilot is going to find all
the key elements in this mail and
present them to us so we can create a
complaint order. This uh really
streamlines the process of creating a
complaint and saves the customers a big
amount of time when they have to handle
complaints from their customers. This is
an area that our customers usually want
to spend the least amount of time on.